Many years ago, when I started my own journey into the Quran,
I found myself having a lot of questions as I read the translation.
How come there's so much repetition in the Quran? This was already talked about
why is it being talked about again? How come there's no chronological order?
How come some chapters are long and some are short?
How come they're not in some sort of subject order?
Uh,
And how come, you know, there's a story and it's only a little bit over here
and then some little bit over there and some little bit over there again,
and questions like these kept popping up in my mind as I read the text.
It wasn't like any other book that I had ever read.
And so as I started exploring the answers to these questions,
I realized that not only were the answers to
these questions some things that make the Quran unique,
but it actually is something that makes the Quran truly divine.
It's incredible.
And it's humbling that what started off as criticism became the very reason that I
was strengthened in my faith that this book can only be from Allah.
This is what inspired me to create my first ever Quran course called Divine Speech.
I traveled around the world teaching it and actually what I feel
this is the second step that I would like you to take in your journey to the Quran,
going through that course that I created to answer these and more questions.
The purpose of it by the end of this course is two things.
One, you learn things about the Quran that you might not have known before,
of course.
And two that, you're going to come out saying, Wow, this can't be from a human being.
This has to be divine.
It will reinforce your faith and confidence in
the divine beauty and power of the Quran.
So let's begin this journey: Divine Speech.